Jeff Caldwell

Web Developer

Profile

I am a web developer and student who makes fast, accessible, great-looking web sites and web apps.

I love working with Javascript, HTML, CSS, and frameworks like Svelte to make projects that help people get things done, but my understanding of the fundamentals of the web platform and my technical skills, coupled with my years of experience in fast-paced and detail-oriented newsrooms gives me a unique perspective into the needs of users and helps make me a perfect fit for any team.

Work History

Digital Executive Producer

August, 2021 - Present

- Leads the digital content team to produce local news and deliver stories across platforms.
- Creates and executes content strategy to improve engagement and audience metrics on the core website and social media.
- Contributes custom HTML, CSS, and JavaScript in stories where appropriate.

Digital Content Producer

July 2019 - August, 2021

- Built and maintained custom streaming control and broadcast graphics playout software using Svelte, JavaScript, and WebSockets.
- Built a custom prompter for use in a digital-only live streaming studio.
- Oversaw the creation, technical execution, and production of live streaming and video content.

Multimedia Journalist

February 2019 - July, 2019

- Researched and developed engaging local stories for broadcast news.
- Produced, reported, shot, wrote, and edited video content.

347-278-5088 nemo.omen@gmail.com http://jeffcaldwell.news 2229 Coleman St San Angelo, TX, 76901

Skills

Knowledgable

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Svelte

Familiar

C++

Java

Technical Writing

Education

Angelo State University

Jan 2021 - Present

Majoring in computer science

Howard College

Jan 2019 - Dec 2020

Associate degree in communication

Websites

https://trainingmontage.dev

https://nemo-omen.github.io